[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many youthful offenders were housed at the Wilkinson Home for boys in the film Sleepers?", "correct_answer": "780", "incorrect_answers": ["725", "673", "537"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wood, water, air, wax, natural gas, paper, cardboard and leather are all renewable resources.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many languages does Rosie, the protagonist of Princess Protection Program, speak?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "8", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1995 Bruce Springsteen song, The Ghost of Tom Joad gets its title from a character in a book by this author.", "correct_answer": "John Steinbeck", "incorrect_answers": ["Agatha Christie", "Ernest Hemingway", "William Faulkner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Uranophobia is the fear of heaven.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these creatures continues to consume milk as an adult in the wild?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Bear", "Primate", "Platypus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term means fear of spiders?", "correct_answer": "Arachnophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Xanthophobia", "Vitricophobia", "Zelophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a bo diddley?", "correct_answer": "A home-made guitar", "incorrect_answers": ["A sandwich common to poor people", "A rock and roll band", "A home-made microphone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tympanoplasty is a type of reconstructive surgery performed on which part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Eardrum", "incorrect_answers": ["Fingers or toes", "Skull bones", "Knees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Bruce Willis character in the movie Lucky Number Slevin?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Goodkat", "incorrect_answers": ["John MC Clain", "Korbin Dallas", "Sonny Truelove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be of other religious beliefs besides Christianity?", "correct_answer": "70", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "60", "80"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the car of the gang leader Clarence Boddicker in the movie RoboCop.", "correct_answer": "6000 SUX", "incorrect_answers": ["1987 VW", "Project X", "Bertha"]}]